untappedcities.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy | Untapped Cities

Your privacy is important to us at Untapped Cities, LLC (“we”, or “our”). Accordingly, we have established and implemented information handling practices for [untappedcities.com](https://untappedcities.com/) (the “Site”) that we believe are consistent with the highest standards and best practices of organizations doing business on the Internet. This Privacy Policy describes the practices that apply to the Site, including, specifically, the information we collect about you, when and how we collect that information and what may happen to that information. We have prepared this detailed Privacy Policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions about how you use the Site. Capitalized terms in this Privacy Policy have the meaning ascribed to them in our [Terms of Use](https://untappedcities.com/terms-of-use/). For European Union privacy information, click [here](https://untappedcities.com/eu-privacy-information/).

### When You Visit The Site

You can always visit the Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information. When you visit the Site we do collect usage information, but it is anonymous and is not linked to you as an individual. We may use this data to better understand, for example, how the Site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at the Site, the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors and the Internet Protocol addresses from which our visitors connect to the Site. We may use this information to improve the Site’s Content and ease of use.

### When You Become a User

When you sign up as a User, you provide us with information such as your name, email address, zip code and other contact information. We may use the information you provide on or through the Site to improve the Site’s Content and ease of use, or as you otherwise consent in advance. We will take all reasonable efforts to protect this information. However, you acknowledge and agree that we may provide your personal information (a) to third-party providers of services to the Site, such as computer programmers and technicians, provided that they are under obligation to us to protect this information, (b) to other third parties when compelled by a court order or other legal process, (c) to partners who provided services or experiences to which the user attends or books a ticket for.

### Security

The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We safeguard the security of the data you send us with physical and electronic procedures. However, it is not possible to guarantee the security or integrity of information disclosed online. Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet, including when you are using the Site.

### When You Post Content

Users may post or upload User Content to the Site. As between you and us and between other Users and you, you are the owner of all User Content that you upload, email or post to or within the Site. You grant us permission to use your User Content on and in connection with the Site. For more information, see the Site’s [Terms of Use](https://untappedcities.com/terms-of-use/).

### When You Submit Feedback to Us

In order to submit comments or questions to the site, you will have to register for a user account, a process that involves, among other disclosures, the provision of your email address. We will not disclose your email address or other personal information to third parties, except as expressly set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may contact you via the email address you provide to answer your question(s), clarify the information you have submitted and send you emails, from time to time, as part of our Email List. (For additional information, see [Terms of Use ](https://untappedcities.com/terms-of-use/).

### **Collection of Information**

**Information You Provide to Us**

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you register for an Untapped Cities account, sign up for a subscription, participate in any interactive features of the Sites, subscribe to a newsletter or email list, participate in a survey, contest, promotion or event, order or purchase (either for yourself or for another person) meal ingredients or other products made available through the Sites (collectively, the “ _Products_ ”), apply for a job, communicate with us via third party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us.

The types of information we may collect from you include:

(a) **  Account Information**, such as your name, email address, password, postal address, phone number, subscription, delivery and dietary preferences and any other information you choose to provide;

(b) **  Transaction Information**, such as information about the Products you purchase, shipping and delivery information and information related to returns, refunds and cancellations. We may also collect and store limited payment information from you, such as payment card type and expiration date and the last four digits of your payment card number; however, we do not collect or store full payment card numbers and all transactions are processed by our third party payment processor.

(c) **  Information About Others**, such as the names and email addresses of gift recipients when you purchase gifts through the Sites or invite friends or family to try the Sites or Products.

(d) **  Other Information You Choose to Provide**, such as when you participate in a survey, contest, promotion or interactive area of the Sites or when you request technical or customer support.

**Information We Collect Automatically**

When you access or use the Sites, the types of information we may automatically collect about you include:

(a) **  Log Information**: When you visit the Sites, our servers automatically record certain log file information, such as your Internet Protocol (“ _IP_ ”) address, operating system, browser type and language, referring URLs, access times, pages viewed, links clicked and other information about your activities on the Sites.

(b) **  Mobile Device Information**: We collect information about the mobile device you use to access or use the Sites, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information and information about your use of our mobile applications. With your consent, we may also collect information about the location of your device and access and collect information from certain native applications on your device (such as your device’s camera, photo album and phonebook applications) to facilitate your use of certain features of the Sites. For more information about how you can control the collection of location information and/or our access to other applications on your device, please see “Your Choices” below.

(c) **  Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**: We and our service providers use various tracking technologies, including cookies and web beacons, to collect information about you when you interact with our Sites, including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve the Sites and your experience, see which areas and features of the Sites are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in the Sites or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.

**Information We Collect From Other Sources**

We may also obtain information about you from other sources and combine that with information we collect directly. For example, we may collect information about you when you post content to our pages or feeds on third party social media sites, or if you use credentials (e.g., username and password) from a third party site to create or log into your Untapped Cities account.

_**Use of Information**_

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

(a) Provide, maintain and improve the Sites and Products;

(b) Manage your account and send you related information, including confirmations, updates, technical notices, security alerts and support and administrative messages;

(c) Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;

(d) Communicate with you about the Sites, Products, recipes, services, offers, surveys, events and other news and information we think may be of interest to you;

(e) Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with the Sites;

(f) Detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of Untapped Cities and others;

(g) Personalize and improve the Sites and provide advertisements, content and features that match your profile or interests;

(h) Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards;

(i) Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with a better experience; and

(j) Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

Untapped Cities is based in the United States, and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Sites or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

_**Sharing of Information**_

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

(a) With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;

(b) We may make our postal address list available to certain third parties we believe may offer products or services of interest to you;

(c) When you participate in the interactive areas of the Sites or interact with us on third party social media sites, certain information that you provide may be displayed publicly, such as your name, photos and other information you choose to provide;

(d) In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, rule, regulation or legal process;

(e) If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our Terms of Use or other policies, or to protect the rights, property or safety of Blue Apron or others;

(f) In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, acquisition, sale of assets or any business, other change of control transaction or financing;

(g) Between and among Untapped Cities and any current or future parent, subsidiary and/or affiliated company; and

(h) With your consent or at your direction.

We also may share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

### Cookies and Pixel Tags

We, or a third-party advertiser acting on our behalf, may place a “cookie” or “pixel tag” on your personal computer when you come to the Site or visit a site on which we advertise. These devices are small computer files that our computer sends to your computer and that your computer sends back to us each time you visit the Site. We may use these devices to collect data to help us personalize and improve your experiences on the Site. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit. If you decide not to accept our cookies, your ability to use some features on the Site may be impaired.

### Third-Party Advertisers

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).

### Links to Third-Party Websites

The Site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of the websites that you visit. Our Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site and does not cover information collected elsewhere.

### California Privacy Rights

Pursuant to California Civil Code §1798.83, a California resident who has provided personal information to a business with which he/she has established a business relationship has the right to request from that business information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom such personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed, upon receipt of a request by a California resident. However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right. As noted above, we do not disclose such personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure.

### Modifications to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change the terms, conditions, and notices in this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@untappedcities.com](mailto:info@untappedcities.com)

_Last updated as of March 5, 2018._

© 2018 Untapped Cities, LLC
